A Guide to the John Wells research notes, 1871-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Miscellaneous notes, 1871-2006., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 48-69)
  - Reading List, Introduction to the History of Construction Technology and Tool Marks, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Rectified Photography and Photo Drawings for Historic Preservation, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Researching Your Historic Virginia Property, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds Metals Company Headquarters, undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Richard B. Russell Project Area, Georgia, undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Richmond (Virginia) Architects, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Cold Storage Complex, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - The Rise of the Skyscraper and the Fall of Louis Sullivan, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Roanoke (Virginia) Architects, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Rogers, Edgerton Stewart, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Rosemont Historic District, undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Russell, Charles T., undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Sanborn Fire Insurance Maps, undated (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Santee Canal (Berkeley County, South Carolina), 1981 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Serviceberry Press, 1998 and undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Serviceberry Press, Proofs, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Serviceberry Press, Proofs, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Shoppell's Modern Houses: An Illustrated Architectural Quarterly, 1890 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Sirrine, Joseph E., 1911-1947 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Skyscrapers in South Carolina, 1984 and undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Society of Architectural Historians (SAH), 1975-1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - South Carolina Architects, 1885-1935, draft, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - South Carolina Architects Research Project (SCARP), 1985-1991 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - South Carolina Architects with Rehabilitation/Restoration Experience, 1984-1985 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - South Carolina County Courthouses, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - South Carolina, Iron Manufacturers and Cast Iron Storefronts, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - South Carolina State Gazetteer, notes, undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Spartanburg (South Carolina) Architects, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Stadtenbauliche Vortrage, 1913 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - State Route 71 (South Knoxville Boulevard, Tennessee), Historic Architecture Assessment 2000 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church (Roanoke, Virginia), 1988 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - St. Lawrence Lumber Company, undated (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - St. Mary Help of Christians Church (Aiken, South Carolina), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - St. Mary Help of Christians Church (Aiken, South Carolina), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - St. Stephen's, A Gothic Revival Episcopal Church, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Study of United States Army Family Housing, Standardized Plans (PX-0001-5-0835), 1986 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - ummer Field Projects, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Sumter County Courthouses 1954, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Survey of State Owned Properties: Institutions of Higher Education, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Tax Aspects of Historic Preservation, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Robert R., undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee Architects, draft, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee Architects, draft, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Tennessee Architects, draft, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Tennessee Bed and Breakfasts, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Tennessee's Capital Cities and the Tennessee Stae Capitol, 1967-1975 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee References in the Goodspeed Histories of Arkansas Counties, draft, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee Registered Architects, Roster, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - "There Is Not Even a Bad One": The Architects and Near-Architects of the New South, undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Tony P. Wrenn Collection, New Hanover County Public Library, North Carolina, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Truss Bridges, report, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Tuck Pointing, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - University of Virginia, Bibliographies, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - University of Virginia, School of Architecture, Class Listings, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - University of Virginia, School of Architecture, Syllabi, 1975-1977 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Vernacular Architecture Forum, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Vernacular Architecture Forum, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Vernacular Architecture Forum, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Architects, 1835-1955: A Biographical Dictionary, draft, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Architects, Cover Design, 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Architects, Portsmouth Buildings, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Housing Network, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Registered Architects, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Virginia State University, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Walter Scott Montgomery House (Spartanburg, South Carolina), 1984 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Washington, D.C., Architects, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - West of Boulevard Historic District (Richmond, Virginia), undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Williams Place (Spartanburg County, South Carolina), 1983 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Charles Coker, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Wilson County Courthouse (North Carolina), undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Wilson & Wilson, undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Women in Architecture, 1886-1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Woodland Heights Historic District, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Woodland Heights Preservation Plan, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Wood, Waddy B., undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - World War II: Memories of the USS Alaska (CB-1), draft, 1995, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - "(Our) Working Drawings", undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - X-Ray Examination of Historic Structures, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Youngers, Clays, Crenshaws and 919 West Franklin Street, Richmond, Virginia, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Series IV. Architectural Drawings, 1906-1982, undated., Extent: 1 map case drawer.
  Series IV. Architectural drawings, 1906-1982. Includes drawings mostly drafted by Wells, but contains a few outliers.
  - Arrows Farmhouse, Albemarle County, Virginia, 1979 (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Black Mingo Baptist Church, Williamsburg County, South Carolina, 1981 (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 2)
  - CSS Ironclad Virginia (Merrimack), 1937 (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 3)
  - Estouteville, Albemarle County, Virginia, John Fornaro, Architect, undated (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
  - Fleming M. Fox Residence, Ashland, Virginia, Ashland Powers Fox, Architect, undated (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 5)
  - HABS Sample Sheets, US Depatment of Interior, undated (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 6)
  - Lower Gassaway Bridge, Pickens County, South Carolina, undated (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 7)
  - Richmond High School, Charles K. Bryant, Architect, 1906 (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 8)
  - Sams House, Datha Island, South Carolina, 1982 (Map-case 6, Drawer 8, Folder 9)